



　:¨·.·¨:
　`·.　this font was made by me, using my own handwriting ꒰ ू´ ˘ ` ू ꒱
   
　　・ it supports english, portuguese, and basic japanese ( hiragana & katakana )

　　・ this font is for personal use only, please don't use it commercially

　　・ crediting me when using is not necessary, but appreciated !

　　・ please do not edit my font or remove the credits

　　・ you may redistribute my font anywhere you like, but please include this .txt file



						middlepot.com
						︶︶︶︶︶ꔫ︶︶︶︶︶